# **RESUME**

### **AASTHA SINGH**

+91 90768 81846

Email.id: aasthasingh1412@gmail.com

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/aastha-singh-7479191a7



### **OBJECTIVE**

A motivated individual looking forward to obtaining a position where my experience and education can be utilized and expanded, using my skills and abilities to contribute positively towards my personal as well as growth of the organisation.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Gurugram Estate Pvt Ltd.

(HR Executive)

March 2024- present

- Recruiting for sales profile and others.
- Day to Day operations.
- Attendance and leave management.
- Onboarding.

**Obtener Virtual services** 

(Human Resource Manager)

July 2023 - Feb 2024

- Recruiting for miultiple positions.
- Day to Day operations
- Salary, Attendance and leave management.
- Onboarding and Exit Management.

#### Unext

(Senior admission officer)

Nov 2022 – May 2023

- Resolving student queries
- converting Prospects into Customers
- Maintaining the Data

Internship – Vinosha portfolio

( Hr executive)

Internship – RAS Media & Entertainment

( Hr executive)

#### **EDUCATION QUALIFICATION**

COURSE	COLLEGE/INSTITUTE	UNIVERSITY	PERCENTAGE	YEAR OF PASSING
PGDM (HR)	Noida institute of engineering and technology (NIET)	NIET ( greater noida)	70%	2023
BBA	Hierank Business School	Chaudhary Charan Singh	65%	2021

		University (Meerut)		
12 <sup>th</sup>	Vinayak Academy	NIOS	70%	2017
10 <sup>th</sup>	Gramodaya	CBSE	8.6 cgpa	2014
	international college			

## **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

- A study on Mobile/ e-banking services of SBI
- Market Research Projects (Technology in Management)
- Market Research Project (Average salary of employee at malls)
- Market Research Project (Rent and Area of Store outlets)
- Consumer buying behaviour (Telecom service)

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

• Certificate/ Experience letter of RAS media and entertainment.

## **SKILLS**

- Recruitment
- Talent acquisition
- Clear Communication
- HR Operations management